yfull.com 2013-09-20

# 

Please read this document ("Privacy Policy & Terms and Conditions") carefully!

Through access to the website, located on the Internet at http://www.yfull.com, sub-domains (based on it, similar to subdomain_name.yfull.com) and any of its pages, you thereby agree to unconditionally comply with the terms of use (Terms). If you do not agree, then immediately leave this site and stop using of the service offered.

YFull.com respects your privacy and will not disclose your personal information without your consent.

By registering on the Website, or order the service, you confirm that you have read, understood and realized the level of confidentiality and agree to abide this Agreement. YFull.com administration reserves the right in its sole discretion to change and (or) supplement these Terms at any time without prior and (or) further notice. The actual text of the User Agreement located at: WWW.

**1\. Terms and Definitions**

1.1 The site - a set of web pages located on the Internet who share the theme, design, a single address space domain www.yfull.com, i.e. navigation and physically located on the same Web server.

1.2 The domain address space yfull.com - a virtual space on the Internet, available at the second level domain name http://www.yfull.com and third level domain names third_level_name.ufull.com.

1.3 "Service" or "Services" - services provided on a commercial basis, include any product or service sold (or provided at no cost) to You by us (special products, personal services, website, mobile application and software).

1.4 Visitors (Visitor) - any person having access to the site via the Internet.

1.5 Registered users (User) - a person who paid any of the offered services and received personal account to the website.

1.6 Client - User who has paid any of the services offered by the Service.

1.7 The Owner of the site (YFull.com) - "YFull Team"

1.8 User pages (personal page) - section of the site, accessible only to the user, whereby the user to control their account. 

1.9 Content - open and (or) closed significant information content site - text, graphics, multimedia, etc. 

1.10 "Personal information" - is information which can be used to verify Client (User) identity, either alone or in combination with other information.

1.11 "Self-Reported Information" is all information about yourself

1.12 "Registration Information" is the information you provide about yourself when obtaining a login. 

1.13 "Web Behavior Information" is information on how you use the YFull.com website (e.g. browser type, domains, page views) collected through log files, cookies, and other web technology.

**2\. Registration with the Site, use of the Site and service offerings**

2.1 Upon activation (registration on the Site) User is required to provide some relevant information about themselves (Registration Data), including name, address, email, phone, and other information. The user is responsible for the provision of reliable information to update the personal data in case of any changes.

2.2 Adding additional information is optional, and by the User at will.

2.3 By submitting your personal data during registration on the Site, a feedback form, as well as the time of booking service, the user consents to the handling of both using automated and without the use of automation. ser agrees to use the information received from it the personal information of the site and the Service in order to ensure that the requested services in a generalized form, as well as to carry out marketing and statistical research, despite the fact that the registration data (name, email address, contact details, IP, etc.) will not be disclosed to third parties. Site handles personal data: for registration (activation) of a user on the site, to fulfill their obligations to the user (mailing, in technical support) for assessment and analysis work of the website;

2.4 The User shall fully responsible for the safety of their user name and password and not transfer or provide to third parties. All actions performed on the site owned by the user with the login and password information, and any consequences that could cause or caused them for such use, it is considered quite a User.

2.5 User alone, and with the help of the Administration, periodically update the registration data and other personally identifiable information that was provided at registration, to ensure its accuracy, currency and completeness. 

**3\. Using of Personal and Registration Information**

3.1 YFull.com collects, maintain, and use Personal Information solely as permitted by law.

3.2 YFull.com use information from you for the purposes that are necessary in our work and to ensure the smooth operation of your account and/or access to our services. The objectives (purposes) are: to provide you with our services; improve our services, including the supply of new products and/or services; to inform and invite you to participate in a specific research projects; connection with you to obtain a certificate; other advertising goals; the implementation of measures to control quality, conducting other studies after obtaining your consent.

3.3 YFull.com use Registration Information to enable Clients purchase, inform Client when his Genetic Information is available to him, provide him with customer service, manage YFull.com Services, and authenticate Client/User website visits and usage.

3.4 YFull.com use Web Behavior Information to track and monitor aggregate usage of our website. If Client/User give us consent to participate in YFull.com Research, Client/User Web Behavior Information may be used and disclosed to third parties in aggregate form for YFull.com Research intended to be published in peer-reviewed scientific journals. If Client/User do not give consent to participate in YFull.com Research, YFull.com may still use Client/User Web Behavior Information for research purposes, which may include disclosure of aggregated Web Behavior Information to third-party non-profit and/or commercial research partners who will not publish that information in a peer-reviewed scientific journal.

3.5 Except as otherwise set forth herein, YFull.com will never release your individual-level Genetic and/or Self-Reported Information to a third party without asking for and receiving your explicit consent to do so, unless required by law.

**4\. Information Disclosure**

4.1 We make every reasonable effort to protect your privacy as described in this Privacy Policy. Nevertheless, we may be required by law to disclose your personally identifiable information.

4.2 We may disclose to third parties, and/or use in our Services, "Aggregated Genetic and Self-Reported Information", which is Genetic and Self-Reported Information that has been stripped of Registration Information and combined with data from a number of other users sufficient to minimize the possibility of exposing individual-level information while still providing scientific evidence. If you have given consent for your Genetic and Self-Reported Information to be used in YFull.com Research, we may include such information in Aggregated Genetic and Self-Reported Information intended to be published in peer-reviewed scientific journals. We emphasize that Aggregated Genetic and Self-Reported Information will be stripped of names, physical addresses, email addresses, and any other Personal Information that may be used to identify you as a unique individual.

4.3 We may disclose to third parties - Yfull.com. Partners or service providers (e.g. our contracted genotyping laboratory or credit card processors) use and/or store the information in order to provide you with YFull.com's Services.

**5\. How to Contact Us**

5.1 Questions about this Summary, our Privacy Statement, or about YFull.com's handling of your Personal Information may be emailed to @yfull.com
